



# EDUCATION AND TRAINING

#### Full Stack Web Developer

Information And Technology Helsinki Business College, Helsinki Expected in May 2023

#### Master's degree

Public Health University of Eastern Finland, Kuopio January 2017

#### **LANGUAGES**

Nepali: First Language

English: C1

Advanced

Finnish: A2

Elementary

Hindi: B2

Upper Intermediate

#### LINKEDIN

# **ANUPA THAPA**

#### **SUMMARY**

Aspiring full-stack web developer looking for growth opportunities. I have 4+ years of experience managing various projects and conducting scientific research. I decided to transition to software development for new challenges and personal growth. Well versed in agile methodology, I am excited to bring my project management and research skill to software development.

## **SKILLS HIGHLIGHTS**

- HTML5, CSS,
- Frontend: JavaScript and React.
- Backend: PHP and Symfony.
- Databases: MariaDB, MongoDB
- CMS: Headless Drupal with React
- Unit testing and quality assurance: Jest, Peer review

- · Prototyping: Figma
- UI libraries: React Bootstrap, Material UI
- RESTful services/APIs
- Version control: Git, GitHub
- Others: Docker, AWS, CI/CD pipelines, Jenkins, Lando

# **SOFT SKILLS**

- Open-mindedness
- · Enthusiastic and quick learner
- Collaborative, accountability and ownership.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **UI/UX TRAINEE**

Turku Bioscience | Turku | January 2023 - Current

• Creating product designs and prototypes using Adobe XD.

#### **VISITING RESEARCHER**

THL | Helsinki, Finland | November 2019 - December 2021

• Studied sleep health and diet correlation

#### **INTERN**

World Health Organization | Switzerland | March 2016 - June 2016

• Technical support to implement agile methodology in emergency management

https://www.linkedin.com /in/anupathapa/

# **GITHUB**

https://github.com/anupa87

#### **REFERENCES**

Margit Tennosaar margit.tennosaar@bc.fi +358 (50) 374 5468

Santosh Kalwar santosh.kalwar@bc.fi +358 (44) 775 6412

### **PROJECT COORDINATOR**

UNICEF Nepal, Nepal | January 2013 - August 2013

#### **COMMUNITY SOLUTION LEADER**

IREX | New York, USA | July 2012 - December 2012

#### **PROJECT COORDINATOR**

Plan, Nepal | Nepal | November 2010 - June 2012

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

- Getting started with DevOps on AWS, AWS training and certification -2022
- AWS technical essentials, AWS training and certification 2022
- Introduction to Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (EC2), AWS training and certification 2022
- Introduction to AWS CodeCommit, AWS training and certification 2022
- Composer, SymfonyCasts 2022
- PHP namespaces, SymfonyCasts 2022